Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - Correspondence, 1940-2021; circa 1970-2021; Series 1 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains general, professional, and personal correspondence, thank you notes, and greeting cards between E. Ethelbert Miller and his various contacts. There are folders which contains material sent to and from various members of the Miller family. This subseries also contains copies of manuscripts and other works sent to Miller for comment, review, or just to share--however, this material has been restricted. The material dates from 1940-2021. The original portion of this subseries contained correspondence between E. Ethelbert Miller and his mother Enid Miller from 1967-2000, as well as his "Survival Letters" correspondence with June Jordan from 1977-1989. Much of the more recent correspondence are in the format of emails sent to and from Miller, which he has printed out.
    - Don Mee Choi (1/2), 1990-2012; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Don Mee Choi (2/2), 1990-2012; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence Enid Miller, 1940-1941; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence love letters from Eddie Miller to Enid Marshall, 1940-1941; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Enid Miller, 1967-1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Enid Miller, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Enid Miller, 1974-1978 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Enid Miller, 1977-1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Enid Miller, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Enid Miller, 1986-1997 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Enid Miller, 1989-2000 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Enid Miller, 1989-2000 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Enid Miller, 1989-2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - June Jordan: the Survival Letters, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - June Jordan: the Survival Letters, 1978-1998 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1987; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1992; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1993-2010; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence [1/3], 2009 April 15 - 2011 September 8; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence [2/3], 2011 September 13 - 2011 November; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence [3/3], 2011 November 14 - 2011 December 7; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Postcards to Enid and Egberto Miller, 1970-1999; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - postcards, 1993-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - postcards, 2001-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1983-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: With Family, 1969-1996; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1978-1991; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1992-2002; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2005-2008; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2009-2014; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence (1/2), 1972-2012; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence (2/2), 2013-2015; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - greeting cards, 2000-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - greeting cards, 2009-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 1972-1987; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 1988-1990; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 1991-1993; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 1994-1999; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 2000-2006; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 2007-2009; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence about Readings and Events, 2010-2013; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, circa 1983-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, undated; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Birthday cards, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Birthday cards, Circa 1990-2018; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Birthday cards, Circa 1990-2018; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Thank You Letters to Miller, 2005 June; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Personal correspondence, undated; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Personal correspondence, undated; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2013-2015; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 2015; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972-2018; Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1974, 1979, 1983, 1985, 1992, 1998, 1999-2003, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1990, 1999-2001, 2004-2007, 2010, 2012-2013, 2019-2020; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2003, 2004, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1998, 2004, 2007, 2014; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2017-2019; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence [1/2], 2020; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence [2/2], 2020; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 2020, 2021, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence to Denise King, 1973-1978; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and article related to Sterling Brown, 1978, 1996-1997, 2000, 2014; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from Edwidge Danitcat (writer), 1995-1997, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from Poet Jane Hirshfield, 2001, 2003, 2005, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence from Veronique Tadjo, 2000, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Greeting cards, 2018; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Greeting cards, 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Greeting cards and letters, 2003, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Greeting Cards and letters [1/2], 2018-2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Greeting Cards and letters [2/2], 2018-2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Greeting Cards and letters, 2019; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Greeting cards, letters, and postcards, 1981, 2016, 2020, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and materials between Anna Johnson and Ethelbert Miller [1/2], 1986-1992, 1995-1997, 1999-2000, 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and materials between Anna Johnson and Ethelbert Miller [2/2], 1986-1992, 1995-1997, 1999-2000, 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Ethelbert Student Letters and Info [Student Letters and Event Materials] [1/2], 1999-2009, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Ethelbert Student Letters and Info [Student Letters and Event Materials] [2/2], 1999-2009, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Publishing and Appearance Agreements and related correspondence, 2018-2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: Adisa, Opal Palmer, 1994; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: Maggio, Mike, 2019; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Raisor, Philip, 2019; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: Roberts, Kim (sent for review), 2019; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Sweig, Julia, 2020; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: Tallie, Mariahadessa Ekere (Mariah), undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: Taylor, Merideth M., 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: Thompson, Clifford, 2015; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: Wright, Jay, circa 2013; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Wright, Jay, 2021; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript and correspondence from Martin Lammon, 1997-1998; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Various manuscripts, poems, and works sent to Ethelbert Miller, 1989, 2020, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - Oversize materials, 1975-2000; Series 1 Subseries 7
    This subseries dating from 1995-2001 contains oversize material including posters, publications and clothing.
    Arranged in chronological order
    - Proclamation of E. Ethelbert Miller Day, County of Madison Tennessee, 5/21/2001 (Box 67, Item 1)
    - Poster: Live! @ Your Library, 9/8/2001 (Box 67, Item 2)
    - Poster: Modern Masters Reading Series 2001-2002, 2004-2002 (Box 67, Item 3)
    - Poster: The Writers Center Reading Series, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Item 4)
    - Poster: Longwood Authors Series, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Item 5)
    - The Handprint Identity Project, 12/12/2008 (Box 67, Item 6)
    - Poster: Metro Muse, Literary Heritage Series, undated (Box 67, Item 7)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 1 number 1, 5/1975 (Box 67, Item 8)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 1 number 3, 10/1975 (Box 67, Item 9)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 2 number 1, 1976 (Box 67, Item 10)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 2 number 2, 1976 (Box 67, Item 11)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 2 number 4, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Item 12)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 3 number 1, 1977 (Box 67, Item 13)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 3 number 3 (Box 67, Item 14)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 3 number 4, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Item 15)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 3 number 5, 1978 (Box 67, Item 16)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 3 number 6, 1978 (Box 67, Item 17)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 4 number 3, 1978 (Box 67, Item 18)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 4 number 4, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Item 19)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 4 number 6, 1979 (Box 67, Item 20)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 5 number 1, 1979 (Box 67, Item 21)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 5 number 3, 1979 (Box 67, Item 22)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 6 number 1, 1980 (Box 67, Item 23)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 6 number 4, 1981 (Box 67, Item 24)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 7 number 5, 1982 (Box 67, Item 25)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 8 number 4, 1983 (Box 67, Item 26)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 8 number 6, 1988 (Box 67, Item 27)
    - Washington Review of the Arts, volume 9 number 2, 1988 (Box 67, Item 28)
    - T-shirt: Bennington Summer Writing Workshop, 1994 (Box 68, Item 1)
    - Baseball hat: Bronx, undated (Box 68, Item 2)
    - Baseball hat: Emory & Henry College, undated (Box 68, Item 3)
    - Appreciation Award from Phi Delta Kappa International, Chapter 51, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Awards: Various Certificates, Plagues, and Medals, 1995-2009; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Flat box 154)
    - Award: Proclamation of E. Ethelbert Miller Day, County of Madison Tennessee, 2001 May 21; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Flat box 155)
    - Posters: Various, 1989-2008; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Flat box 155)
    - UHV/ABR reading series E. Ethelbert Miller, November 3 no year provided; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - University of Bahrain plaque, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 177)
  - Posters, 1973-2003; Series 1 Subseries 8
    Arranged by size
    This subseries containes posters dating from 1973-2010. Note that there are posters in the Overisze series as well as this series.
    - White Fields Press poster, 1996; 5 Linear Feet; 5 linear feet (Tube 1)
    - Black Writers Reading Series, 2/17/1993 (Tube 1)
    - The Nancy Morejon Poetry Tour, 4/1985 (Tube 1)
    - Sweet Honey On the Rock, 11th Anniversary concert, undated (Tube 1)
    - Amelia House poem, signed, 3/23/1988 (Tube 1)
    - 1998 Fall Writers Series (Tube 1)
    - African American Poets of Washington D.C. Past and Present, 1978 (Tube 2)
    - 11th Annual University of Delaware Black Artists Festival, undated (Tube 2)
    - Whispers, Secrets and Promises reading, undated (Tube 2)
    - Welcome President Nyerere Karibu Ndugu, 8/1977 (Tube 2)
    - Howard University 1st Annual Symposium on Creative Expression, 1973 (Tube 2)
    - Artist rendering, undated (Tube 2)
    - Catholic Poetry Reading, undated (Tube 3)
    - D.C. Public Library 2nd Annual Citywide Book Club, Fathering Words, 2003 (Tube 3)
    - The National Conference of Afro-American Writers, 4/1976 (Tube 3)
    - Central Michigan University 27th Annual Black History Month, 1999 (Tube 3)
    - 7th Annual Mirbed Festival, 1986 (Tube 4)
    - Fathering Words, undated (Tube 4)
    - Forerunners: Black Poets in America #2, 5/1972 (Tube 5)
    - Howard University Celebrates W.C. Handy and the Blues Tradition, 11/1973 (Tube 5)
    - Renwick Galleryof the National Museum of American Art Second International Poetry Festival, undated (Tube 5)
    - National Book Festival, 10/4/2003 (Tube 5)
    - The American Writers Congress, 10/1981 (Tube 5)
    - Open Poetry Readings at the IMF Visitor's Center, undated (Tube 5)
    - International Poetry Festival, 2/4/1985 (Tube 6)
    - A Story to Tell, 2/18/1998 (Tube 6)
    - Affirmative Acts - June Jordan, 1999 (Tube 6)
    - Southern Festival of Books, 10/13/2000 (Tube 6)
    - Phoenix Public Library Author Series, 4/17/2003 (Tube 6)
    - Promotional Event Posters, 1975-2012; Series 1 Subseries 8 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - A Celebration of African American Poetry with Ethelbert Miller (Box Series 1 Subseries 8 Box 196)
  - Personal materials, circa 1940-2020; circa 1980s-2010s; Series 1 Subseries 9
    Arranged loosely alpahbetically by each accession. This results in repetitive alphabetical lists that usually follow box order.
    This subseries contains biographical and family content, as well as materials related Miller's teaching work. It also contains physical items including pinback buttons, t-shirts, and hats. In addition to the daily planners, journals, and notebooks contained in this subseries, there are similar items in Subseries 4, which may overlap in date or fill in gaps. The material is dated from 1940 to 2020.
    - Personal Materials: About, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Personal Materials: Awards and Certificates, 1965-2013; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Personal Materials: Contributins and Donations to the University of Minnesota, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - E. Ethelbert Miller Datebook, 2001; series 1 subseries 9 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Personal Materials: Ethelbert Miller's Bibliography, n.d., undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Personal Materials: Family Materials, Undated; Series 1 subseries 9 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      Folder contains original birth documents.
    - Personal Materials: General History of Rap and Hip Hop, 1992-2003; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Personal Materials: Greeting Cards, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Personal Materials: Guestbook, 1982 September 25; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 177)
    - Personal Materials: Miller Children's Graduation Programs and Certificates, 1993-2009; Series 1 Subseries 0 (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Personal Materials: Photographs, Circa 1957- Circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      There is a small group of early family pictures given to Ethelbert by his mother. He says the are of Ethelbert and his father.
    - Personal Materials: Photos of Children's Gradutations, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Personal Materials: Report Cards and Commencement Programs, 1962-1966; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Personal Materials: Plaques (Photocopies of), 1965-2001; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Personal materials, 1998-2016; series 1 subseries 9 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Personal Family Materials, 1999-2015; Series 1 Subseries9 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Teaching: Black Artists-Resumes (visual), Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Teaching: "Blacks in the Arts" Course Description, 1984 Fall; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Teaching: Lecture Notes and Transcripts, 1979-1993; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Teaching: Material Related to Ethelbert's Tenure at George Mason University, 2006; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Teaching: Mitsutoshi Inaba: Cover Letter and Curriculum Vitae, 2013 March 11; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Teaching: Resumes, undated; Series 1, Subseries 9 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - Teaching: Special Project Flyers from Howard University, 1977-1978; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Teaching: Syllabi, Lecture Notes, and Exam Questions, 1993-2003; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Plaques and awards, Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 160)
    - Class photographs, 1957-1961; series 1 subseries 9 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence & Review Draft, 1986-2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Family Papers, 1987-2009; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - High School Thank You Notes, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Marie Hunter Correspondence, 1977-1996; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: family, Circa 1940-2009; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, 1951-2009; series 1 subseries 9 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, undated; series 1 subseries 9 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Photographs Ethelbert Miller, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Photographs Richard Miller [Ethelbert's borther], Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Marie [Ethelbert's sister], Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Pins/buttons, circa 1990; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    - T-Shirt, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - T-shirt, circa 2000; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - T-Shirt, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Thank You Letters, 1997-2003; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Various Arts and Personal Materials, 1998-2013; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Various arts and personal materials, 1970-2016; series 1 subseries 6 (Box 180, Folder 10)
    - Identification cards and business cards, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Incoming correspondence, 1997-2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Incoming correspondence, 2001-2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1984-2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, 1963-1996; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Reflections on Ethelbert, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Notebooks, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks, 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Notebooks, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Notebooks, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks, 2012; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Notebooks, 2013; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Notebooks, 2016-2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Notebooks, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Calendar, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - 50th year book, 2001; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Calendar, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Calendar, 2017; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Blues People: Negro Music in White America by LeRoi Jones (advanced proofs), 1963; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - The collected poems of Ethelbert Miller (a list) count 315 as of 2/2/2015, Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence [1/2], 1974-2019; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence [2/2], 1974-2019; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Dark Room Collective, 1990-2013; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Draft: If God Invented Baseball, Circa 2018; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Draft: The Ear is an Organ Made for Love, Circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Essay for Ethelbert Miller Tribute by Becky Thompson, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - inter-Governmental Philatelic Corp., 1997; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Lou Stovall, Circa 1991; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 20)
    - Mosaic Theater Company, 2018; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 21)
    - Negro History Week, 1936 February 09; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 22)
    - A Negroes Plea or The Great Problem in Poetry (reprint), Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 23)
    - Notes: The Black Artist Commitment + Responsibilities, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 24)
    - Oliver LaGrune, 1967-1982; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 25)
    - Playbills, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 26)
    - Poetry for the Advanced: Amiri Baraka, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 27)
    - Poems -- Sandy Esteves, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 28)
    - Scrapbook, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 29)
    - Speaking in Tongue poems by Robert Fleming, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 30)
    - Walt Harrington, 1987-1990; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 31)
    - Walter Mosley Alien Script, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 197, Folder 32)
    - 1968 Anchor Yearbook, Christopher Columbus High School, MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - August Wilson materials, 2000, 2005; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Barack Obama Inauguration Mementos, 2008-2009; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Course Materials 492.1, Spring 1993, 1993, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Course Materials, Goucher College, 2018, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Course Materials, "Understanding Contemporary African American Poetry", undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Family Correspondence, 1982, 1986, undated; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Leopold Sedar Senghor, President of Senegal, visit to Howard University, 1975 May 23; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 9 (Box 206, Folder 3)